

GENDER

FEMALE

DATE OF BIRTH

JANUARY 23, 1996

NATIONALITY

PHILIPPINES

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH & FILIPINO

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Garcia Collece of Technology

PHILIPPINES

JUNE 12, 2012 - APRIL 2016

CERTIFICATIONS

FOUNDATIONS OF USER EXPERIENCE (UX) DESIGN

COURSERA | GOOGLE CERTIFICATE ID: **SEB236SZ7BER**

FEBRUARU 24, 2022

RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN

FREECODECAMP.ORG

JUNE 12, 2012 - APRIL 2016

THE FUNDAMENTALS OF DIGITAL MARKETING

GOOGLE
CERTIFICATE ID: **TCM T8D 7GY**MARCH 23, 2021

SOCIAL



LINKEDIN

LINKEDIN.COM/IN/THATGIRLNATHALIE/



DRIBBBLE

DRIBBBLE.COM/THATGIRLNATHALIE



INSTAGRAM

INSTAGRAM.COM/DESIGN.NATHALIE/



GITHUB

GITHUB.COM/THATGIRLNATHALIE

NIÑA NATHALIE MASIGON

PRODUCT DESIGNER



+971 55 508 7380

HELLO@NATHALIE.DESIGN

HTTPS://NATHALIE.DESIGN

O DEIRA, DUBAI, UAE

ABOUT

Designing products for Fintech and E-commerce businesses with a Bachelor's degree in Information Technology. Skilled in Design Systems and Prototyping. Completed several projects, including Visual Search & Product Discovery, E-commerce Order Returns, Checkout Process Redesign, and worked with industry-famous brands like Mumuso, Muy Mucho, Brands for Less, and Edenred to name a few.

SKILLS

UI/UX DESIGN	HTML 5
VISUAL DESIGN	CSS 3 (SCSS/LESS)
INTERACTION DESIGN	BOOTSTRAP 3, 4 & 5
RAPID PROTOTYPING	TAILWINDCSS
WIREFRAMING	JAVASCRIPT

TOOLS

FIGMA	SKETCH	ADOBE XD	INVISION	AC	ADOBE PHOTOSHOP		
ADOBE	ILLUSTRATOR	ADOBE PREM	IIERE PRO	NPM	VISUAL ST	UDIO CODE	
GIT	MICROSOFT OFFI	CE TRELLO	NOTION	SLA	ACK MS	TEAMS	

EXPERIENCE

2022 - PRESENT

R

2018 - JAN 2022

Š

PRODUCT DESIGNER

EDENRED UAE

Business Bay, Dubai, United Arab Emirates

- o Developed a new design system and revamped the entire B2B Portal (Payroll+); worked closely with the Head of Experience and Design
- o Collaborated with developers to monitor their progress with design implementations
- o Owned and led all B2B Payroll Portal overhauls, designed the MVP, and contributed to the product vision of Payroll+
- Worked closely with product managers to wireframe and come up with design solutions and manage the usability risk by testing designs with clients before development

PRODUCT DESIGNER

BFL GROUP (BRANDS FOR LESS, FZCO)

Jebel Ali Freezone, Dubai, United Arab Emirates

- o Conceptualized and created UX design deliverables to provide a seamless user experience based on business objectives and requirements: user flows, wireframes (lo-fi and hi-fi) and prototypes
- Liaising with back-end developers to ensure web and app logic is properly integrated
- Maintained and generated asset libraries and ensures that they are based on optimal web preferences



GENDER

FEMALE

DATE OF BIRTH

JANUARY 23, 1996

NATIONALITY

PHILIPPINES

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH & FILIPINO

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Garcia Collece of Technology

PHILIPPINES

JUNE 12, 2012 - APRIL 2016

CERTIFICATIONS

FOUNDATIONS OF USER EXPERIENCE (UX) DESIGN

COURSERA | GOOGLE CERTIFICATE ID: SEB236SZ7BER

FEBRUARU 24, 2022

RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN

FREECODECAMP.ORG JUNE 12, 2012 - APRIL 2016

THE FUNDAMENTALS OF **DIGITAL MARKETING**

GOOGLE

CERTIFICATE ID: TCM T8D 7GY

MARCH 23, 2021

SOCIAL



LINKEDIN

LINKEDIN.COM/IN/THATGIRLNATHALIE/



DRIBBBLE

DRIBBBLE.COM/THATGIRLNATHALIE



INSTAGRAM

INSTAGRAM.COM/DESIGN.NATHALIE/



GITHUB

GITHUB.COM/THATGIRLNATHALIE

o Designed engaging, responsive and lead-generating landing pages for campaigns like ramadan, black friday sale, singles day, as well as catalog pages for brands like Toys for Less, Homes for Less, Tchibo, Mumuso & Muy Mucho and converts them to HTML & CSS and ensures stability across devices i.e. desktop, mobile, tablet

o Updates and maintains the CMS for scheduling of campaigns, and fixing any functionality issues, including optimizing images for maximum speed and scalability during execution

PROJECTS UNDER BFL GROUP:

Brands for Less Website & Mobile App

https://www.brandsforless.ae/en-ae/

O Redesigned the Brands for Less mobile app and website's checkout, my orders and order return page user flows based on research and customer feedback

- O Designed Brands for Less websites' visual search feature and collaborated with the dev team to identify product brief and functionality related to business objectives
- o Produced an interface design for quick and easy product filters with a usercentered approach to improve the user flow for a seamless customer experience.

Tchibo / Mumuso / Muy Mucho

o Designed lead-generating *landing pages* and promotional campaigns like newsletters, sale catalogs, social media collaterals according to their brand identity and standards.

WEB DESIGNER 2018

ISERVE

- AUG

2017

틱

2016 - JUN 2017

3

Dubai, United Arab Emirates

- o Modified existing website from layout to function and publish engaging content, such as e-marketing campaigns
- O Developed and design artwork for marketing materials for web or social medias including posters, flyers, company profile, etc.
- O Submited weekly and occasional newsletter to customer database using mailchimp

DESIGN INTERN

PHILIPPINE AIRLINES, INC.

Kalibo, Aklan, Philippines

- o Built rich media graphics for of all marketing and sales presentation
- o Interprets creative briefs to create strong concepts and innovative designs.
- o Worked with a team of designers to prepare multiple design mock-ups and
- O Performs other duties as assigned by management

NOTABLE FREELANCE PROJECTS

2020-PRESENT

SEÑOR GROOMING LOUNGE

Dubai Festival City, United Arab Emirates

https://senorgrooming.com/

- O Transformed "Coming Soon" Landing Page Design to a Responsive Website
- O Replicated original design from the Web for Mobile (or smaller screens) using resources provided.

RYT PARTNERS

Jebel Ali Freezone, Dubai, United Arab Emirates

https://www.rytpartners.com/

O Coordinated with the design team to incorporate responsive design into the landing page.

DENTCARE & THERABREATH CENTER

Kalibo, Aklan, Philippines

O Designed the user flows, journey maps and visual styles for a dental website and carried out adaptive mobile screens for a seamless user experience.